Hallelujah!
I want to start from the viewers.
Wherever you are, whatever situation you are in remember with God all things are possible.
Yes!
With God all things are possible.
Believe first and see.
Viewers say, "I believe!"
I believe!
I can't hear you!
Congregation: I believe!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever situation that you are in...viewers all over the world.
Those of you who are under the influence of my voice, whatever situation that you are in
Whatever situation that you are in...be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Be delivered in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being delivered!
I can see you being rescued!
What is your situation?
Are you sick?
Every dry bone receive!
In your blood.
In your fluid.
In your tendons.
In your bones.
In your kidney.
Receive!
Receive light!
Be revived!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Viewers all over the world,
wherever you are and what ever you are doing;
those of you who are under the influence of my voice, listen!
Jesus said, "I pray that your faith will not fail."
What does this mean?
This means that there will be some factors and issues that will challenge your faith.
It could be sickness.
It could be setback.
It could be affliction.
It could be persecution.
It could be temptation.
Right now I say to you, "be delivered in the name of Jesus!"
Whatever factor, whatever issue that is challenging your faith....be delivered!
He said to Simon "I pray that your faith will not fail you."
What is good for Simon is good for you!
What is for Simon Peter is for you!
Whatever factor, whatever issue that is challenging your faith...be it sickness...be it poverty...be it hardship
be worry..be delivered!
Be delivered!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Whatever factor or issue (that you are facing), it does not mean that you re not a christian.
Don't misjudge yourself because of challenges.
By saying that you are not a christian because you have a sickness.
By saying that you are not a christian because of persecution or whatever challenge you might be facing.
Have faith in God!
Jesus is aware.
He said, "In this world, there will be tribulation.
Cheer up, I have overcome the world."
Rejoice!
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today;
and stay up today with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service, and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV...changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.